Narrator: 1
Stella: All Quiet on the Western Front is on Netflix.
Have you seen it?
Paul: The German one that won lots of Oscars not so long ago? Yes, I have.
And I’ve read the book.
The book’s better than the film, I think. It’s a classic!
Stella: Do you mind watching it again with me?
I really want to see it.
Narrator: 2
Matt: Have you read the Sherlock Holmes books?
Tom: No, I haven’t.
There are so many of them! Life’s too short!
Matt: Have you watched Sherlock?
Tom: Yes, I’ve watched the first three seasons, and I’ve downloaded the fourth.
Narrator: 3
Lexi: Have you seen Les Misérables? The musical, I mean.
Mason: I’ve seen the film, but I haven’t seen it at the theatre. I’d love to go.
Lexi: Let’s book tickets, then. I’ve read the book and I love the music!